<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Hello</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello World</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="textview_is_cleared">TextView is Cleared!!</string>
    <string name="student_information">Student Information</string>
    <string name="tech_activity">Tech Activity</string>
    <string name="webview_activity">WebView Activity</string>
    <string name="form">Form</string>
    <string name="calculator">Calculator</string>
    <string name="status_bar">Status Bar</string>
    <string name="order_t_shirt">Order T-shirt</string>
    <string name="birthday_card">Birthday Card</string>
    <string name="button_activity">Button Activity</string>
    <string name="gander">Gander</string>


    <string-array name="tech_array">
        <item>Android</item>
        <item>Java</item>
        <item>Php</item>
        <item>Python</item>
        <item>C++</item>
        <item>Ruby</item>
        <item>Ajax</item>
        <item>Rails</item>
        <item>.Net</item>
        <item>Perl</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="tech_array_subtitle">
        <item>Android is a mobile operating system based on a modified version of the Linux kernel and other open-source software, designed primarily for touchscreen-based mobile devices such as smartphones and tablets.
        </item>
        <item>Java is a high-level, class-based, object-oriented programming language that is designed to have as few implementation dependencies as possible.
        </item>
        <item>Php is a general-purpose scripting language geared towards web development. It was originally created by Danish-Canadian programmer Rasmus Lerdorf in 1993 and released in 1995. The PHP reference implementation is now produced by the PHP Group.
        </item>
        <item>Python is a high-level, general-purpose programming language. Its design philosophy emphasizes code readability with the use of significant indentation. Python is dynamically typed and garbage-collected. It supports multiple programming paradigms, including structured, object-oriented and functional programming.
        </item>
        <item>C++ is a high-level, general-purpose programming language created by Danish computer scientist Bjarne Stroustrup.
        </item>
        <item>Ruby is an interpreted, high-level, general-purpose programming language. It was designed with an emphasis on programming productivity and simplicity. In Ruby, everything is an object, including primitive data types. It was developed in the mid-1990s by Yukihiro "Matz" Matsumoto in Japan.
        </item>
        <item>AJAX, or Asynchronous JavaScript and XML, is a group of web development techniques that allow web applications to send and receive data from a server without reloading the entire page
        </item>
        <item>Ruby on Rails is a server-side web application framework written in Ruby under the MIT License. Rails is a model–view–controller framework, providing default structures for a database, a web service, and web pages.
        </item>
        <item>NET is a secure, reliable, and high-performance application platform. C# is the programming language for .NET. It\'s strongly-typed and type-safe.
        </item>
        <item>Perl is a high-level, general-purpose, interpreted, dynamic programming language. Though Perl is not officially an acronym, there are various backronyms in use, including "Practical Extraction and Reporting Language".
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="dept_array">
        <item>CSE</item>
        <item>EEE</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>